Thank you for watching!
Yes!!! So, yes, our second guest has started.
I'm gonigonizing. What are you doing?
There was a hair on it, so he had it removed, and then he started on his own.
Now that the hairs have been removed, our second guests are Nakayama-san and Kobayashi-san from Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
Yes! I'm Kaho Kobayashi and Riko Nakayama from Ebisu Chugaku.
Welcome.
I'm sorry to disturb you. It's been a long time. But, although, your last live...
That's right. When are you coming?
All the time, I said, no, Mr. Takei hasn't come.
I always had the image of Chuei-san coming, and Takei-san not being here...
No, no, no, you are supposed to be gone, in the image.
Yes, he was. When?
Oh, that's right, he's coming.
If you want, he was there with Mr. Takei, wasn't he?
I was there with Mr. Takei, wasn't I?
Separate from Chuei-san.
Did you do something when you were alone?
With Umiki?
Yes! With Umiki-san.
Takegami-san's set.
A rare set.
Why before?
No, no, the other day.
New Year's, right?
Last time was with Umiki and the other Fear members.
Me and the little one.
That's right.
Ouch.
Nakata-san's image is amazing.
Stop it.
Poor little guy.
I'm really, really sorry.
I'll never go back.
Even if you do...
They don't even recognize you anymore.
We talked about how you finally came.
Yes, we did.
You know, Nakayama, I've been thinking since the show, you can't see me anymore, today.
Hope. It's all blurred. It's blurring. Blurred, blurred, blurred. Blah, blah, blah. Who's a ghost?
That's what I'm saying. Yes, you know, at the time of Shonatsu. That's right. Yes, it's Eine Kobayashi, so she really is a shooting star fan.
She's a shooting star fan. Why don't you tell her? Fan club. Fan club. What? Fan club. Yeah.
No way.
I quit.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Um...
If, if, if...
Wait a minute.
If you ask the camera...
Oh, I'm stopping.
Ha-ha-ha.
He replied cheerfully
I got a cheerful reply.
I don't need to be cheerful.
I'm full of energy
Full of energy
"I quit.
Wait, when was that?
I don't know when that was.
A long time ago.
Maybe it was. I thought I'd been in there forever.
Yeah.
I thought maybe, you know, you're still a member, you're still signed up.
I'm sure you're still a member.
I thought that already.
I'm sorry.
Come back full of energy.
Because, you know, you're really, uh, my only, uh...
I don't know how to say it...
This connection between our hearts...
Only Kobayashi...
Only Kobayashi is in our fan club.
Yeah, you know...
Our shooting star.
I thought he cared about us.
I didn't think he quit.
I'm sorry.
A thin thread has been severed.
I'm not sorry.
When I say I'm sorry, I'm being realistic.
I joined the Mere Old Man.
Two in a shrimp shack.
You're in there with me.
Synchronized. Perfectly synchronized.
We got in the same day.
That's...
I mean, at the time, we were just one person in EBITCHU.
But you two are different.
We came in the middle of the day.
And I didn't even know them.
I know them.
You know?
You come into a place you don't know.
You know? I knew it.
He's my senior.
You're getting a little more into it, aren't you?
What?
It's a good idea.
You're getting good at it, aren't you?
That's right.
Hehehe...
He's not supposed to say "punch" anymore.
Ebitu didn't give a punch... but he did his best here.
He doesn't have a punching bag.
That's great! We've got new members!
But they're all just two guys who are not good at commenting.
So in the end Ebitu is just...
We're the ones who do the hard work as a comedian.
Yasumoto, the other day when you were wearing orange...
I made a mistake that I don't know what it means when I said Takei-san talked to me a lot.
I'm sure there are mistakes like that.
I laughed so hard.
Then, you know, you have to be a lucky guy, don't you?
I see.
I'm doing my best.
That was tough.
So you knew about the shrimp stew.
Of course I knew.
How did you two get into Ebichu in the first place?
That's exactly...
Before we joined, there were nine of us in the group, and we were crazy about it.
And then three of them were graduating or transferring schools, so we joined.
Yes, that's right, but what were you doing before that?
Well, we were a limited-time unit called "Team Daioh or Lesser.
Team Daioh or the Lesser Kings?
We were only active for one year.
So that's what you were doing. That's the first I've heard of it.
We formed a group for a volume and a volume, and finally, you know...
one year, and we already have a date to break up.
I see. One year only.
How many people were in your group? Teams.
We were a team of seven.
And then me and Riko...
The day we split up, Riko and I would go into the sea...
It's a little bit like this.
So out of the seven of us...
You mean you were thinking of bringing in someone else?
The big guys.
I'm sure they came to see the lessons and stuff.
So maybe they were auditioning.
You still don't know?
They don't know.
I don't know why they picked me.
I don't know.
I didn't ask.
They said, "Well, you were kind of stiff.
I was just like, "Well, you're a little stiff, so I put you in.
What's that?
I don't know.
And then they'd make a gag about it.
Maybe I went in there because I was really stiff. I don't know. I don't know, that's... Now that I think about it. I'll ask him next time.
It was easy for me to do the show and stuff, because everyone was a solid character. But you created the flow.
No, I didn't make it. But Nakayama wanted to make them cry as much as possible. Oh, so that's what happened.
He said, "You're going to make me cry.
Buh-buh-bah-shh. Manager Sano, right?
He did some kind of a live show... pretty much. He came, and the flowers, and Riko Nakayama...
I'm so glad she did it!
I think there were a few people who saw the show for the first time.
I'm sure there will be a few people who'll see it for the first time, and I'm sure the rest of you know what I mean.
I did a show with Tasusu Ebichu and we did a surprise interview for a part-time job and the manager...
The manager, Mr. Sano, was cold towards her.
I used to support her, but she ignored only Ms. Nakayama.
But he ignored only Ms. Nakayama...
She cried.
I don't like that guy.
He's imitating himself.
You know, Kobayashi...
That was funny, wasn't it?
It went on for 5 minutes.
It's in Akita now...
Mom, sister, and brother all do it.
They do it a lot.
Yeah, because how old were you then?
Oh, I was 14 then, too.
Fifteen or fourteen.
Yeah, and that's the best one.
He was younger than you.
Yes, I was.
Before he was the oldest, he was a high school student.
He was the director and stuff... before that...
Don't go on, don't go on. I'll try not to be like her.
Don't go on and on.
How old is he? Thirteen.
How old did you start? Stardust.
I've been in since I was 12. I'm 11 now.
Oh, I see. So you were already in Stardust before you joined Ebitua, and what did you do?
What were you doing before you joined Stardust? Were there any lessons for good luck? Yes, there were. Did you grow up there?
I was with him, but I was taking lessons with Riko, so I had to take lessons with someone who was taking lessons for good luck, so I didn't have the impression that he was there at all.
I knew she was there, but I didn't know her name,
I knew her name, but I didn't think she came. I had the impression that she never came.
I thought she was slacking off. I wondered what she was doing.
How did you get into the scouts in the first place? Scouting.
You're scouts? Are you guys scouts? We're scouts.
Where? Harajuku.
That's really the main street. There was a Tamagotchi store on Takeshita-dori at the time.
I was shopping at the Tamagotchi store with my family, and when we left, I was approached by someone, and the first person who approached me was Stardust,
The first person who approached me was Stardust, and I found myself in the shop.
Did they suddenly say, "Excuse me"?
A handsome man and a woman with a K included us,
I wondered what was going on, and then I went in.
I wondered what was going on, and then I was in.
I got their business cards.
Yes, I did.
You didn't really know then, did you?
I wanted to do it, to begin with.
I didn't want to do it at all. I wasn't very good at showing off,
I said okay, but my mom said let's go talk to him,
I went to talk to him, but he had already become a member.
That day?
She had already recommended it to me without my mother's knowledge.
Your mother?
My parents?
Yes.
It's a ton of events?
What's that? I'm sorry.
Did you get in?
Yes.
Where's Zhongshan?
Am I on the dumpling line?
I had to go to the bathroom on the stairs in the basement, and I was going down the stairs with my mother, and somehow a bus came down at the same speed as me,
I was wondering if he wanted to go to the restroom, but then he put on his skirt and said, "I'm sorry, it's the stairs. It's not the speed. Please close your eyes. No, stop.
Mace just laughed, and said, "Just go to the bathroom! Say...
Did you pee your pants?
I peed my pants!
Did you pee in time?
Just in time!
I got on the train, calmed down, and looked at Mace,
Restaurant Rust! So I went to talk to him.
But you're only 12 or something, right?
You don't know anything about the office or anything, do you?
No, I don't know. I don't know.
I wanted to get in.
I was interested in that kind of work.
What about Nakayama?
Have you wanted to be in show business since you were 12?
Who were your idols?
I was learning modern Malay.
And my sister who was studying with me...
She was an actress.
I said, "I want to be like her.
So she applied to be a model for my magazine.
You did?
I see.
Then that's a totally different tune.
I always wanted to be an actress.
Not at all.
I thought I'd grown up when I went to a live concert that New Year's Eve.
And then Kobayashi sang the theme song for Mashroute on mc before she sang the theme song.
He said something about a tie-up, like it was the first tie-up in a long time.
Like, "Thank you for the tie-up." I wonder if he's learned about tie-ups recently.
I've memorized it, so I knew it was there.
He was very appealing and mature.
That's where it's important.
Back to the topic at hand, I joined Ebi Junior High.
You two are in the same class, but have you met the other members of Ebichu?
Before or when you were under Daioh...
I went to see a live performance once with Daioh and below.
But that's about it.
Just a hello, really.
We didn't know each other.
But I went to your free shows.
I see.
Did you see him one way or the other?
I saw them one way or another.
Is there some kind of first meeting?
The day I joined was an event at the office.
It was an event like a festival where all the female idols from Momokuro gathered.
Momokuro was going to announce her joining the group at a live performance.
I was greeted by Ebinaka as Hiroka Oyo before the show.
I was greeting her as Ebinaka-san.
But by the time the show was over, I was Ebinaka.
So I greeted him in the make-up room.
Did you see anyone other than Ebinaka at that time?
There were a lot of people there.
I'd like to see a lot of other idols.
That's right.
I see.
How was Nakayama? First time.
I've never met you... or any of the other girls before.
Yeah, but I really liked him. He liked Ebichu.
Are you really going to work with these guys?
Yeah, we're going to be together.
And our show starts in two months, right?
Then I feel like I don't know what's right or left at all.
That's right.
That was our show. What else was there? And what else?
Live performances... You didn't do any other variety shows?
Radio?
Really? You didn't know anything about variety?
I didn't even know what Evival was.
The first thing I did was not Tastus. It was Ebibal.
But I've been watching the two of you and Ebichu, and I'm thinking that maybe you really think I'm a scary person.
I was thinking that maybe he really thinks I'm scary or something.
Especially Nakayama.
Even if you are scary, there was a rumor that Takei-san has dark eyes, so he always wears eyeliner.
It's like you put on a lot of makeup.
That's what Yasumoto told me.
After about six months...
Yasumoto or Takei?
She said you wear eyeliner.
Wait a minute. You always thought so?
Are you ashamed?
Even when we're backstage together.
Yeah.
You're wearing eyeliner?
That's fine. I'm not wearing eyeliner.
No makeup, no makeup.
More like no makeup.
She said that.
That's right, that's right.
That was embarrassing.
That's what people thought of me.
Yeah.
So it was really a gradual process.
Gradually you became friends with everyone.
That's right.
I'm glad I joined Ebisu Rose.
I see.
That's where we became good friends.
My image of Kobayashi is that he's good at getting around, and he's like a puppy, he gets along with everyone.
He's like Yasumoto's disciple. He's still my disciple. He still is.
That's why Yasumoto loves him so much.
Nakayama... I wonder... Nakayama was really absent-minded.
Nakayama's right. You didn't think anything of it. But you got along well with Kobayashi.
They were in the same class. They got along well here, and Kobayashi adored Yasumoto.
I wonder if I have an image of that... how it really was.
Nakayama... how did they get along?
Nakayama... this person was like this... Nakayama... that's right...
Nakayama with someone who's sure about Nakayama
Nakayama I think he got along with everyone without looking at them. Nakamura Who were you afraid of?
NakamuraI want to talk about that time NakamuraThere is no one to be afraid of anymore NakamuraThere is no one to be afraid of
NakamuraI don't know if I was scared of him or if I didn't know how to talk to him.
NakamuraHow should I talk to you because you are my senior? NakayamaWell, as far as Nakayama is concerned...
I think it's hard for people as a whole to relate to each other
All of humanity. Nakamura, we're all in this together. I thought so, too.
Nakamura, I wonder what I should say to you.
That's why I asked the other day.
NakamuraAh, here it comes! Here it comes!
NakamuraLet's find out!